kenresearch.com 2019-07-20

# Privacy Policy: Ken Research

This privacy policy covers the information Ken Research Private Limited ("Platform" and/or "We") collects from the user(s) ("User(s)" and/or "You") of www.kenresearch.com ("Website"). Personal information of a User(s) is collected if the User(s) registers with the Website, accesses the Website or takes any action on the Website. 

**Our Privacy Principles:**  
Providing information to us is your choice. You can choose to have the Personal Information provided by you deleted. You also have the right to access a portable copy of your information available to you at any given time which will be sent to you in a common format within 30 days of your request. You also have the right to opt out of receiving communications from the Platform.  
**1\. Preparation For GDPR**  
We have already maintained a consistent data security as well as protection throughout our company.

**2\. Our preparation includes**  
**• Information Audit**  
doing a data/information audit to recognize and survey what individual data we that we possess, the source of the information, how the information is processed, storage, and if disclosed, to whom and why.  
**• Policies & Procedures**  
Implementation of new data protection policies for meeting the standards of GDPR and relevant data protection laws, which includes:  
**• Data Protection**

our principle arrangement and methodology record for protection of personal information or data has been designed to meet the standards of the GDPR. Responsibility and administration measures are set up to guarantee that we comprehend and prove our commitments and obligations, with a devoted spotlight on protection by plan and the rights of people.

**• Data Retention & Erasure**

we are currently revising our retention policy as well as the schedule for meeting ‘data minimization’ and ‘storage limitation’ principles and that personal information is stored, archived and compliantly as well as ethically destroyed. We are actively working towards putting dedicated erasure procedures in place to comply with the ‘Right to Erasure’ obligation and are conscious of when the rights apply; with exemptions if any, response timeframes and notification responsibilities.

**• Data Breaches**

The breach procedures that we have adopted recognize, survey, research and report any individual information break inside 72 hours of getting to be mindful of the breach. Our robust procedures have been distributed among all our employees so that they’re aware of the necessary precautions to be followed in case of a breach.

**• International Data Transfers & Third-Party Disclosures**

Ken Research Private Limited is currently working on strategies and shielding measures for securing encrypting as well as maintaining data integrity. Our methods will incorporate a persistent survey of the nations with adequate ampleness choices, and additionally arrangements for Binding Corporate Rules; standard information security statements or affirmed implicit rules for those nations without. We shall carry stringent checks with all beneficiaries of individual information to survey and confirm that possess proper shields set up to secure the data, ensure enforceable data subject rights along with having effective legal solutions for information subjects where appropriate.

**• Data Subject Access Request (DSAR)**

The company is actively working on updating the DSAR procedures in line with accommodation of a 30 days’ deadline for giving out the information as requested. The company’s new procedures explain various steps for processing a contact request, all the exemptions and templates for response to confirm submissive, reliable and adequate communications has been carried out with the data subjects.

**• Legal Basis for Processing**  
The Company is working on its entire legal basis to ensure appropriate basis for each related system. Moreover, we are also maintaining records a record of all the data processing activities to ensure our compliance with Schedule 1 of the Data Protection Act and Article 30 of the GDPR is met by us.

**What we collect**  
The information you provide us or could provide us would be the following:  
Your registration details including your unique username and your account password. You’re shipping and billing information as well as any other information pertaining to sale or transactions on the website or information which could be required for invoicing purposes.   
Any transactional information with other users of the website as well as your behavior on the website.   
Details of your visits to the websites and information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies including, but not limited to, your IP address and domain name, your browser version and operating system, traffic data, location data, web logs and other communication data, and the resources that you access.  
Correspondence information in case you have a communication with us over the phone or through mail.   
Survey information in case we ask you to participate in one of our surveys we use for research purposes.   
We may collect personal data from our clients over the course of our business dealings and provision of services to the client.  
Any specific personal information which we may need to collect, either for business or regulatory purposes which would be provided with an option for allowance of permission. 

**Why we are collecting the information**  
Our primary purpose for collecting your data is to provide you with offerings that we believe would be of value to you based on the information that indicates your preferences as well as to best use the various services and features offered in the Website. Our purpose of collection of information is to serve our clients better. We may use the information to contact you for any services provided by the platform or its affiliates or its various service providers or platform business partners and advertisers. The information request might be to record your information and details as permitted and required under applicable laws, statutory direction or judiciary orders. Information collection may also be done to serve various promotion materials and advertising materials to you and such other uses as provided in the privacy policy which you will have the option to opt out of.

**How we would use it**  
We may use the information for transactional emails or to provide you with information, direct marketing, online and offline advertising and other materials regarding products, services and other offers from time to time in connection with the Platform. We may also collect information to track User behavior and preferences for internal analytics from all Users of the Website. The information collected could be used to upgrade our website for the purpose of making it serve our customers better

**How we collect information**  
This information is collected through the use of server log files and tracking technologies to collect and analyze certain types of technical information and may include cookies and web beacons. We may combine your Personal Information, other information and information collected from tracking technologies and aggregate it with information collected from other Users using our Website to attempt to provide you with a better experience on our Website.

**User Right to Opt Out**  
As per our privacy policy, you have the right to request a modification of our communications to have them better suited to your needs. You also have the option to Opt Out from our database, which would entail complete removal of your data from our database within a time frame of 2 weeks from the request; however you may still receive communications during a transitional period whilst your data removal process is underway. If you wish to have the Personal Information that you have provided to us deleted, you can always do so by sending a request to us on the e-mail id of our Customer Services department provided at the bottom of the web page. You may note that deletion of certain Personal Information may lead to cancellation of your registration with the Website and your access to certain features of the Website.

**Third Party Websites and Services**  
The information that you provide us may be shared with third parties if it is generic in content. No personal or sensitive information will be shared without your explicit consent. Users may find links to third party services on our website. We are not responsible for the content shown or your interaction with a third party website. The content on websites of third parties can change and browsing and usage of third party sites is subject to that websites own policies

**Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement**  
The Platform cooperates with mandated government and law enforcement agencies or to any third parties by an order under law for the time being in force to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about You to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process, to protect the property and rights of Platform or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity. Platform may also provide your Personal Information to various tax authorities upon any demand or request from them

**Business Transfers**  
The Website may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will ensure that the personal information you have provided through the Website is stored and used by the transferee in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy and that you are notified of any of the above occurrences in a timely manner

**Grounds for Usage of Personal Information**  
While we guarantee that we will never use your personal information for any operations unless granted explicit permission, we do outline specific circumstances under which we would be made to share, export or utilize your personal information for business processes:

_Consent:_ where you have consented to our use of your information (you will have been presented with a consent form in relation to any such use).  
_Contract performance:_ where your information is necessary to enter into or perform our contract with you.  
_Legal obligation:_ where we need to use your information to comply with our legal obligations.  
_Legitimate interests:_ where we have a legitimate interest in using your data and our reasons for using it and this is not outweighed by any adverse impact on your interests, fundamental rights or freedoms.  
_Legal claims:_ where your information is necessary for us to defend, prosecute or make a claim against you, us or a third party

**Sharing of Information**  
Unless given explicit permission, we do not sell trade or export customer data. We may share generic data which is not linked to personal identification with our business partners and affiliates. We may use third party services to operate on our behalf or to help serve you better. 

**Cookies Policy**  
A cookie is defined as a packet of data sent by an Internet server to a browser, which is returned by the browser each time it subsequently accesses the same server, used to identify the user or track their access to the server. The website uses cookies and web beacons for information collection and storage. By using the website you acknowledge consent for the usage of cookies within the scope of the privacy policy.

**Phishing**  
Identity theft and the practice currently known as "phishing" are of great concern to Platform. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication. 

**Changes to Privacy Policy**  
In order to serve our clients better as well as to ensure the best practices in protection of client data in accordance with regularly changing practices, we may revise our privacy policy at any time. If done so, we will have a notification posted on our website and hence encourage our users to regularly check this page of the website in order to ensure our clients are informed about our data collection and security policy. By Using this website, you acknowledge you that it is your responsibility to be informed about the privacy policy and changes being made in order to be aware of the modifications.

**You’re Rights**

  * As per our privacy policy, our customers providing us with their data have the following rights at their disposal:
  * Request for a portable copy of their data in a common format at any given point of time which will be delivered within 30 days of the request
  * Right to opt out of communications from the organization as well as to have your information deleted entirely
  * Right to provision of the details of the usage of your information
  * Right to restrict how we use your information when a complaint is being investigated
  * Your exercise of these rights is exempt to a higher priority which would include safeguarding public interest such as preventing a crime or in safeguarding our interest, for example, maintaining legal privilege. If you exercise any of these rights we will check your entitlement and respond to you within a month
  * If you are not satisfied with our use of your personal information or our response to any exercise of these rights you have the right to complain to the relevant data protection authority for your country

**Consent**  
By using this website, you acknowledge that you have understood and accepted our terms and privacy policy and give your consent for data collection, processing and export operations which fall within the guidelines of our privacy policy stated above
